MD.TONMOY ISLAM RUHIN

Web Devloper

Wordpress & Custom Devlopment

Email: mdruhinahmed93gmail.com

Call : +880 189002480

Website: tonmoyislamruhin1255.github.io/RuhinAhmed.com/

Objectives:

Hardworking web developer and WordPress expert looking for opportunities to utilize my knowledge to create solutions to clients' website needs with the ability to create elegant solutions in minimum time. Creative thinking, problem-solving, teamwork, and technical skills are my strengths. Self-motivated team player with Three years of experience where I contribute to growing IT teams by applying my advanced knowledge along with my leadership abilities to meet client needs and exceed their expectations.

Recently Completed Project:

1. Medinova is a medical related website.

Live: https://tonmoyislamruhin1255.github.io/Medinova/

2. Healthy which provides guidance through healthy living.

Live: dev-assignmentcourseweb.pantheonsite.io

3. Assura group a real estate business official website development.

Live: https://www.assuregroupbd.com/

4. A Travels agency website development provide custom future.

Live: http://www.newedgeinternational.com/

5. Media-center E-Commerce Website content design.

Live: https://tonmoyislamruhin1255.github.io/Media-center/

Work Experience:

Designation	Company	Responsibilities	Duration	Address
Junior Web	Finvasoft	60%	2019 - 2021	Dhaka
Developer.				
Full Stack Web	Techvila	70%	2021 - 2022	Dhaka
Devloper & WP				
Expart.				

Tactical skills:

Language	Percentage
HTML / CSS	<u>60%</u>
Bootstrap / Tailwind	<u>60%</u>
JavaScript / React / Vue	<u>70%</u>
Php / Laravel / Mysqli	<u>80%</u>
Wordpress	<u>70%</u>

Educational qualification:

Name Of	Group	Year	GPA	Bord /
Examinations	Subject			University
SSE	Science	2018	5.00	Sylhet
HSE	Science	2020	4.29	Sylhet

Training Summary:

Training Title	Topic	Institute	Year	Duration
Learn Web Devlopment With Six Month	Web Design & Devlopment	Programming Hero community	2018	2018-2018

Personal Information:

Name : MD. Tonmoy Islam Ruhin

Father's name : MR. Abdul Basit Bason

Mother's name : MST. Rahena Akther

Date of birth : 11/12/2003

Blood Group : A+
Sex : Male

Marital status : Unmarried
Nationality : Bangladeshi

Religion : Islam

Pregnant Address : Moulvibazer,Sylhet,Bangladesh Permanent address : Moulvibazer,Sylhet,Bangladesh

Hobby : Traveling by bike

Reference:

Name : Jonker Mahmub

Relation: Teacher

Ruhin Ahmed